atelieronweb.com 2012-12-22

# SALES - AtelierOnWeb - privacy policy

**AtelierOnWeb - Informative Note on Privacy Online**

When accessing the site  **www.atelieronweb.com**  managed by  **AtelierOnWebS.r.l. ("AOW")** , or using the content thereof, you accept the terms of the Informative Note on Privacy Online, as shown hereunder. If you do not accept such terms, please do not access the site or use the content thereof.

 **Collection of personal information**

While you carry out activities such as ordering products, download software or participate in competitions,  **AOW  **may ask you to provide personal information by compiling and sending a specific form (electronic form). You are completely free to accept such request or not. Should you decide to comply,  **AOW  **may ask you to provide personal and/or corporate information and other data which identifies you.

**AOW  **collects such information to record it and allow you to take part in the activities chosen by you. If you order a product, for example, this information is used to register the licence and right, where foreseen, to avail of technical support, updates or other advantages which may be offered to registered users.

**AOW  **will use the information provided by you to keep you updated on the new versions of a product, special offers and on other  **AOW**  products and services.

**AOW  **acknowledges and attributes great value to the responsible use of such information.

**AOW  **shall comply meticulously with your instructions.

 **Using cookies and the type of data treated**

When visiting our site  **www.atelieronweb.com** , you may move through the pages anonymously and have access to significant information without revealing your identity. In order to improve our site, we use “cookies” to keep track of your navigation. A cookie is a reduced whole of data transferred to your browser by a Web server which can only be read by the server which carried out the transfer.

_Falling into this category of data are:_

·  the IP addresses of computers used by Users using the service;

·  the number of accesses;

·  the displayed pages;

·  the date and time in which access took place;

·  the duration of stay in the displayed contents.

·  the page of origin before arriving at www.atelieronweb.com

·  the navigation browser;

·  the operating system used.

·  the resolution of the system used.

The data is used for the sole purpose of obtaining anonymous statistical information on the use of the site and to check that it is operating correctly, it is cancelled immediately after processing. Data may be used for assessing responsibility in the case of hypothetical computer-related crimes to the damage of the site: without prejudice to such occurrence, at the current state the data on web contacts does not continue for more than seven days. No navigation datum is diffused.

Almost all browsers are initially programmed to accept cookies. You can set the browser so it warns you when you receive a cookie, allowing you to choose whether to accept it or not (for some Web pages requiring authorisation cookies are not optional. Users choosing not to receive cookies probably cannot access such pages).

 **AOW  **uses the cookies to keep track of your visit to our site  **www.atelieronweb.com**. Our Web servers automatically register the IP/Internet address of your computer. This information does not identify you personally. You shall therefore continue to be anonymous unless you have provided  **AOW  **with your personal information under other forms.

 **Rights of the Involved Party.**

Pursuant to art. 7 of Legislative Decree 196/2003, the Involved Party has the right at any time to obtain from the Holder, or the Manager when named, information on the treatment of their data, the methods and purposes and logic applied to them and the origin thereof as well as:

1) confirmation of the existence of the data and communication and origin thereof;

2) the identification details of the Holder and Managers as well as the parties or categories of parties to which the data may be communicated or which may become aware thereof as Manager or Appointed Persons;

3) the updating, correction and integration of the data;

4) the cancellation, transformation in anonymous form and blocking of data treated in violation of the law;

5) certification that the operations pursuant to points 3) and 4) were brought to the knowledge of those to whom the data was communicated and diffused, with the exception of the case in which such fulfilment proves impossible or leads to the use of means evidently disproportionate respect to the protected right;

6) to oppose: the treatment of data, provided that pertinent to the purpose of the collection, for legitimate reasons; to the treatment of data for the purposes of commercial information or for carrying out market research.

This can be done by writing to  **Altelier98**  at the following address:

**Atelieronweb S.r.l.**  via G.B. Morgagni, 43 63822 Porto S. Giorgio (FM), represented by its pro-tempore legal representative Cesare Dania.

**Holder of the Treatment.**

The Holder of the treatment is:  **Atelieronweb S.r.l.**  with offices in via G.B. Morgagni, 43 63822 Porto S. Giorgio (FM), represented by its administrator and legal representative Cesare Dania. Tel 0734670816 Fax 0734670816 e-mail: info@atelieronweb.com.

**INFORMATIVE NOTE ON THE MATTER OF PROTECTION OF PERSONAL DATA**

[PURSUANT TO ART. 13 LEGISLATIVE DECREE 30.06.2003, No. 196]

In observance of that foreseen pursuant to and by effect of art. 13 Legislative Decree 30 June 2003 (Personal Data Protection Code),  **AtelierOnWeb S.r.l.**  with offices in  via G.B. Morgagni, 45 - 63822 Porto San Giorgio (FM) owner of the site  **www.atelieronweb.com** , as holder of the treatment of personal data, hereby informs the Involved Party of which are the purposes and methods of treatment of the collected personal data, the environment of communication and diffusion thereof, as well as the nature of its conferral. 

The data subject matter of the treatment, collected for the purposes of registration to the newsletter (specifically: e-mail address, name and surname) is treated and used directly for the instrumental purposes of competing the identification of the parties asking to receive updates on the site, in the full observance of the principles of correctness and necessity and the normative in force on the matter.

The treatment of data is performed through computer-related procedures or in any case on-line and never in paper format, by the parties who are purposefully appointed to do so. The data is kept in computer archives to which the minimum security measures are applied as foreseen by the legislator.

The personal data communicated by the registered party is not subject to diffusion or communication. 

The registered party may avail of the rights as expressed in articles 7, 8, 9 and 10 of Legislative Decree 30/06/03 of no.196, holding the legal position of “Involved Party”. Such rights may be exercised by contacting the Holder of the treatment or  **AtelierOnWeb S.r.l.**  represented by its legal representative Cesare Dania according to the following and alternative procedures by e-mail to the address customercare@atelieronweb.com; by fax to no. 0734670816; by ordinary mail to  **AtelierOnWeb S.r.l.**  via G.B. Morgagni, 45 - 63822 Porto San Giorgio (FM) Italy. In particular according to art. 7 the Involved Party may obtain confirmation of the existence or not of the personal data concerning them, if not yet registered, and communication thereof in an intelligible form. The Involved Party furthermore has the right to obtain an indication: a) of the original of the personal data; b) of the purposes and methods of the treatment; c) of the logic applied in the case of treatment carried out with the use of electronic instruments; d) of the identifying details of the holder, managers and designated representative pursuant to article 5, paragraph 2; e) the parties or categories or parties to which the personal data may be communicated or which may become aware thereof as designated representative in the territory of the State, or managers or appointed persons. The Involved Party has the right to obtain: a) the updating, correction or, when of interest, integration of the data; b) the cancellation, transformation in anonymous form or blocking of data treated in violation of the law, including that the conservation of which is not necessary in relation to the purposes for which the data was collected or treated thereafter; c) certification that the operations pursuant to letters a) and b) were brought to the attention, with regard to the content thereof, of those to which the data was communicated or diffuses, with the exception of the case in which such fulfilment proves impossible or leads to the use of means evidently disproportionate respect to the protected right. Lastly the Involved Party has the right to oppose, wholly or in part: a) for reasons legitimate to the treatment of the personal data concerning them, provided that pertinent to the purpose of the collection; b) to the treatment of personal data concerning them for the purposes of sending advertising or direct sale material or for carrying out market research or commercial communication. 

The registered party’s data shall be kept solely and exclusively for the period of registration. Unsubscription from the newsletter shall lead to the elimination of all their data by the treatment Holder. 

Consent to the treatment of data is obligatory in order to be registered for the newsletter and is exhibited by sending the request for registration.

The holder informs that any non communication or incorrect communication of any of the information required for sending updates shall make it impossible for the Holder to guarantee to congruency of such treatment. 

Holder of the treatment is:  **AtelierOnWeb  S.r.l.,** via G.B. Morgagni, 45 - 63822 Porto S. Giorgio (FM) Italy, represented by its pro-tempore legal representative Cesare Dania. Tel 0734670816 Fax 0734670816 e-mail: info@atelieronweb.com.
